const randrCardData = [
    {
        "Front":"AUTHORIZING OFFICIAL",
        "Back":"Senior official with the authority to assume responsibility and accountability for information systems. Only official that can accept risk."
    },
    {
        "Front":"AUTHORIZING OFFICIAL DESIGNATED REPRESENTATIVE",
        "Back":"An organization official that can act on behalf of the AO. CANNOT ACCEPT RISK on behalf of AO."
    },
    {
        "Front":"CHIEF ACQUISITION OFFICER",
        "Back":"Official designated by head of agency. Helps ensure that the mission is met through management of the agency's acquisition activities. Coordinates across the agency ensuring that adequate privacy and security requirements are embedded in acquisition activities."
    },
    {
        "Front":"CHIEF INFORMATION OFFICER",
        "Back":"Responsible for designating a senior agency information security officer. Develops and maintains security policies and procedures. Oversees personnel with significant security and privacy responsibilities. May be an AO."
    },
    {
        "Front":"COMMON CONTROL PROVIDER",
        "Back":"The indiviual or group responsible for implementation, assessment and monitoring of common controls. The Senior Agency Official for Privacy has oversight over the common controls."
    },
    {
        "Front":"CONTROL ASSESSOR",
        "Back":"Entity responsible for the conducting a comprehensive assessment of implemented controls and enhancements to determine their effectivenes. Assessors require a certain level of independence which is determined by the AO."
    },
    {
        "Front":"ENTERPRISE ARCHITECT",
        "Back":"Responsible for working with leadership and SME's to create a wholistic view of the Agency's informations systems, reduce the complexity of the acrhitecture to facilitate security. Serves as part of the Risk Executive (Function)."
    },
    {
        "Front":"HEAD OF AGENCY",
        "Back":"Responsible for providing information security privacy and protections commensurate with the level of risk. The Head of Agency establishes the organizational commitment to required to manage risk."
    },
    {
        "Front":"INFORMATION OWNER OR STEWARD",
        "Back":"Official responsible for the specified information and establishing policies and procedures that govern it. Not necessarily the System Owner."
    },
    {
        "Front":"MISSION OR BUSINESS OWNER",
        "Back":"Senior Official within an organization with specific mission or line of business responsibilities. They are key stakeholders that provide input into the RMF process."
    },
    {
        "Front":"RISK EXECUTIVE (FUNCTION)",
        "Back": "Individual or group that provides a comprehensive, organization-wide approach to risk management. Led by the Senior Accountable Official for Risk Mangement. Common resource for players across the RMF process. Establish how the organization FARM's."
    },
    {
        "Front": "SECURITY OR PRIVACY ARCHITECT",
        "Back": "Responsible for ensuring the stakeholder protection and privacy needs are adequately addressed in the enterprise architecture. Serves as the primary liason between the enterprise architect and the systems security and privacy engineers."
    },
    {
        "Front":"SENIOR ACCOUNTABLE OFFICIAL FOR RISK MANAGEMENT",
        "Back":"Leads Risk Executive (Function) and is responsible for aligning security and privacy risk management processes."
    },
    {
        "Front":"SENIOR AGENCY INFORMATION SECURITY OFFICER",
        "Back":"Responsible for carrying out the CIO security responsibilities under FISMA. Primary liason for the CIO to the organizations AO's."
    },
    {
        "Front":"SENIOR AGENCY OFFICIAL FOR PRIVACY",
        "Back":"Senior official with agency wide responsibility for ensuring compliance with applicable privacy controls."
    },
    {
        "Front":"SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR",
        "Back":"Individual, group or organization responsible for maintaining systems and system elements."
    },
    {
        "Front": "SYSTEM OWNER",
        "Back":"Organizational official responsible for the procurement, development, integration, modification, operation, maintenance, and disposal of a system."
    },
    {
        "Front":"SYSTEM SECURITY OR PRIVACY OFFICER",
        "Back":"Inidividual responsible for ensuring that the security and privacy posture of the system is maintained. The princiapl advisor on all matters involving the controls for the system."
    },
    {
        "Front":"SYSTEM USER",
        "Back":"Individual or (system) process acting on behalf of an individual that is authorized to access information and information systems to perform assigned duties."
    },
    {
        "Front":"SYSTEMS SECURITYOR PRIVACY ENGINEER",
        "Back":"Individual, group, or organization responsible for conducting systems security or privacy engineering activities as part of the SDLC."
    }
    
    
]


export default randrCardData;